So this is what my solution looks like.
إذًا هكذا يبدو الحل الذي أنفذه.
I put each of the three elements on its own line because I think it's easier to
وضعتُ كلًا من العناصر الثلاثة في سطره الخاص، وأعتقد أنه من الأسهل
read like this.
القراءة هكذا.
Either way it is actually valid one line or
أيًا ما كانت الطريقة التي نستخدمها ففي الواقع يُتاح استخدام سطر واحد
three lines but I like this way a little bit more.
أو ثلاثة أسطر فحسب؛ لكني أحب هذه الطريقة أكثر قليلًا.
Notice that I have opening tags and
لاحِظوا أن لديّ علامات افتتاحية
closing tags with content in between for each of my three elements.
وعلامات إغلاق وبينها المحتوى لكلٍ من عناصري الثلاثة.
Also notice that my closing tags look different because they
أيضًا لاحِظوا أن علامات الإغلاق لديّ تبدو مختلفة، لأن جميعها يتضمن
all have a slash here after the less-than sign.
شرطة مائلة هنا بعد علامة أصغر من.
So let's see how this looks.
إذن دعونا نرى كيف يبدو هذا.
I've saved my file and I will come over to the browser and I will hit refresh.
لقد حفظتُ ملفي وسأتجه إلى المستعرِض وأضغط refresh.
And there you go, notice that the p tag that says I'm Cameron
بينما تتجهون إلى هناك لاحِظوا أن العلامة p التي تقول I'm Cameron
is all on its own line, there is nothing next to it.
توجد بالكامل في سطر مستقل ولا شيء بعدها؛
But the two spans that say I like teaching, and
بينما علامتا الامتداد اللتان تقولان I like teaching
web dev :) are all on the same line.
وweb dev :) جميعًا في نفس السطر.
Remember, this is a paragraph, so it wants to be by itself.
تذكَّروا أن هذه فقرة، لذا ترغب أن تكون مستقلة بذاتها،
But spans are part of a line, so they are part of a line.
بينما علامات الامتداد هي جزء من سطر لذا هي أجزاء من سطر.
That's why I left this space right here.
لهذا تركتُ هذه المسافة هنا.
So, that goes to show you a couple things.
والهف من ذلك أن أريكم شيئين:
One, is that it's really not too bad writing these things.
الأول أن كتابة هذه الأشياء ليست بالغة السوء في الواقع،
And two, every type of element will display differently.
والثاني أن كل نوع من العناصر سيُعرض بشكل مختلف.
You'll be learning all about the different elements and
ستتعلمون كل ما يخص العناصر المختلفة
the way that they display later on.
والطريقة التي يُعرضون بها فيما بعد.